[{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678922470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":39228,"timeElapsed":136733},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678939275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":16802,"timeElapsed":153538},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678958030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":18753,"timeElapsed":172293},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678975619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":17587,"timeElapsed":189882},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":14667,"timeElapsed":204552},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679000438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":10147,"timeElapsed":214700},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679006164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5724,"timeElapsed":220427},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679014029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7863,"timeElapsed":228292},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4669,"timeElapsed":232963},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679040121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":16758,"timeElapsed":254383},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679044916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4794,"timeElapsed":259179},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679049501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4583,"timeElapsed":263763},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679053129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3626,"timeElapsed":267391},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679057279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4148,"timeElapsed":271542},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679061715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4434,"timeElapsed":275978},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679065852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4135,"timeElapsed":280115},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679071667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5814,"timeElapsed":285930},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679075307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3638,"timeElapsed":289570},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679099585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":21903,"timeElapsed":313848},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679106728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7141,"timeElapsed":320991},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679113264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6534,"timeElapsed":327527},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679118942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5676,"timeElapsed":333205},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679124669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5726,"timeElapsed":338932},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679129777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5105,"timeElapsed":344040},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679141122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":11343,"timeElapsed":355385},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5055,"timeElapsed":360442},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679151956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5775,"timeElapsed":366219},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679166555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":12722,"timeElapsed":380818},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679193472,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":26914,"timeElapsed":407734},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6744,"timeElapsed":414481},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5789,"timeElapsed":420272},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679212882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6870,"timeElapsed":427145},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679223084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":10200,"timeElapsed":437347},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679228626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5540,"timeElapsed":442889},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679235685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":7056,"timeElapsed":449948},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5578,"timeElapsed":455528},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679246023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4755,"timeElapsed":460285},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679257278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8247,"timeElapsed":471541},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679261528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4248,"timeElapsed":475791},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679266510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4981,"timeElapsed":480773},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679270549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4037,"timeElapsed":484812},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679274115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3564,"timeElapsed":488378},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679277259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3142,"timeElapsed":491522},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679283261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":6000,"timeElapsed":497524},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679288468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5206,"timeElapsed":502731},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679292159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3689,"timeElapsed":506422},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679315459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":19720,"timeElapsed":529721},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679326296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":10835,"timeElapsed":540559},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679336820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":10523,"timeElapsed":551083},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679345980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":9157,"timeElapsed":560242},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679355375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":9393,"timeElapsed":569638},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679362383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7006,"timeElapsed":576646},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679371964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9579,"timeElapsed":586227},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679377903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5937,"timeElapsed":592166},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679383222,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5317,"timeElapsed":597485},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679389981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4385,"timeElapsed":604244},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679395897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5914,"timeElapsed":610160},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679402458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6559,"timeElapsed":616721},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679414002,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11542,"timeElapsed":628264},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679417693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3689,"timeElapsed":631956},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679423284,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5590,"timeElapsed":637547},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679426552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3267,"timeElapsed":640815},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679432505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":5951,"timeElapsed":646768},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679439203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6696,"timeElapsed":653466},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679445093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5888,"timeElapsed":659356},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679460291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":13257,"timeElapsed":674554},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679463658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3366,"timeElapsed":677921},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679467399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3739,"timeElapsed":681662},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679470816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3415,"timeElapsed":685079},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679479427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8610,"timeElapsed":693690},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679482596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":3167,"timeElapsed":696859},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679488238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5640,"timeElapsed":702501},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679492563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4323,"timeElapsed":706826},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679495918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3354,"timeElapsed":710181},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679508208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":9939,"timeElapsed":722471},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679512346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4137,"timeElapsed":726609},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679519094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":6746,"timeElapsed":733357},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679523394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4298,"timeElapsed":737657},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679529767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6371,"timeElapsed":744030},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679533930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4162,"timeElapsed":748193},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679539049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5117,"timeElapsed":753312},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679546492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":7441,"timeElapsed":760755},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679552244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":5750,"timeElapsed":766507},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679563229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":9096,"timeElapsed":777492},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679567927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4696,"timeElapsed":782190},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679570685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2756,"timeElapsed":784948},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679574288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3601,"timeElapsed":788551},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679578016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3726,"timeElapsed":792279},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679580601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2583,"timeElapsed":794864},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679584888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4285,"timeElapsed":799151},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679587970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3080,"timeElapsed":802232},{"subjectID":"306ssuuyjr","prolificID":"67371b28ce8dec57ac9fc2cc","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b20f88a2d43f53bcc08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679592281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4310,"timeElapsed":806544}]